<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Temperature Gauge (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.TemperatureGauge</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/TemperatureGauge</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Aeryl mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=843504745

- Added a wall-mounted gauge, since people asked for it and I liked the idea!
- Added the current temperature in the description of a selected gauge
- Added the current temperature in the description of a selected switch
- Testing this with the Parallel Power-grid mod gave no errors so it should now be compatible
- Russian translation added, thanks uncleshvya

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
	[tr]
		[td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
		[td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/TemperatureGauge][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]

Adds a simple buildable thermometer that displays the current ambient temperature and can be configured to provide temperature based alerts. You can set it to alert you when a room gets too hot or cold. If you have ever had food rot in a freezer or plants die in your greenhouse because you forgot to check the temperature, this mod is for you.

German Translation by Lauri7x3!

It should be fine to add this mod to an existing save.

[b]Updated to 1.0.0[/b] (22 Oct 2018):
• Updated for version 1.0
• Now supports Fluffy's Mod Manager.
• Switches now update less frequently; this should provide a slight increase to performance.


[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>